Enzo Vezzaro

UI / UX designer and Web developer



enzovezzaro05@gmail.com



Los Angeles Open to move



Bē behance.net/enzovezzaro





323 829 1027



github.com/EnzoVezzaro



endesign.co



Hello, I'm Enzo. I love being creative, exploring and broadening my horizons, doing things in high quality and giving stunning user experience in my products. I'm an enthusiast of user interface, experience design, and clean and usable coding.

Experiences

September 2014 - Present

Freelance Web Designer

Static Websites with HTML, CSS, and Javascript

June 2011 - Dicember 2011

Front-End Developer, UI Designer Cercami.it

Valdagno, Italy

Education

2012 - 2014

Computer Science Degree (in process)

Los Angeles City College

Los Angeles, California

2006 - 2010

Multimedia and Communication Diploma

I.P.S. Americo D'Aschio

Vicenza, Italy

Languages

Spanish: Native

Italian: Native

Tools

Mac OS X Atom Sketch Adobe Suite Slack Trello Git

Design Skills

Mobile design Interaction design Photography **UI** animations Prototype design Web design Responsive design



Development Skills

□ • □ HTML, CSS, SASS, JADE, Gulp, Foundation, Bootstrap Materialize Javascript, jQuery Git Java

Hobie













